Contact

+8613095933832 (Mobile) akintoyekolade0@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ akintoyekolade (LinkedIn) koladeakintoye.vzy.io (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Creative Design
UX Design/Strategy
Responsive Web Design
Figma (Tool)
HTML5
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
JavaScript

Kolade Akintoye

Creative Designer / Architectural Designer

Ningbo, Zhejiang, China

Summary

A desiger with a diverse skill set encompassing Graphic & Brand design, Motion design, architectural design and UI/UX Design, committed to pushing boundaries and crafting unique, memorable experiences through visual designs. I combine technical skills, artistic vision, and strategic thinking to deliver innovative and visually cohesive solutions.

Experience

Top Universe
UI/UX Design trainee
March 2023 - March 2024 (1 year)

COLOGENY (Volunteer)
Graphic Designer
February 2022 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Abeokuta, Ogun State, Nigeria

School of Virtue (NGO, Volunteer)
Video Editor
June 2019 - Present (4 years 11 months)
Nigeria

Freelance

Freelance Designer
January 2017 - Present (7 years 4 months)

- Developed brand identity & visual guidelines for brands.
- Created social media designs for individuals and brands.

Healthphilic (Internship) - Remote Graphic Designer January 2023 - April 2023 (4 months)

Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria

Revohub Technologies Video Editor May 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 9 months)

Education

Ningbo University

Bachelor of Architecture - BArch, Architecture · (2019 - 2024)